/*! For license information please see 8.3551943d.chunk.js.LICENSE.txt */
(this["webpackJsonphacktj-2021"]=this["webpackJsonphacktj-2021"]||[]).push([[8],{164:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),r=n.n(a),o=n(3),i=n(29),s=n(5),l=n.n(s),c=n(27),u=n.n(c),d=n(28),f={tag:d.i,fluid:l.a.oneOfType([l.a.bool,l.a.string]),className:l.a.string,cssModule:l.a.object},p=function(e){var t=e.className,n=e.cssModule,a=e.fluid,s=e.tag,l=Object(i.a)(e,["className","cssModule","fluid","tag"]),c="container";!0===a?c="container-fluid":a&&(c="container-"+a);var f=Object(d.f)(u()(t,c),n);return r.a.createElement(s,Object(o.a)({},l,{className:f}))};p.propTypes=f,p.defaultProps={tag:"div"};var h=p,m=n(6),w=n(7),g=(n(61),function(e){var t=e.question,n=e.answer,a=e.small,o=void 0!==a&&a,i=r.a.useState(!1),s=Object(w.a)(i,2),l=s[0],c=s[1],u=function(){return c(!l)};return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"".concat(l?"is-open":"")},r.a.createElement("h3",{className:"question ".concat(o?"small":"")},r.a.createElement("button",{type:"button",onClick:u},t),r.a.createElement("span",{className:"icon icon-plus",onClick:u,onKeyDown:u,role:"button","aria-label":"Show answer",tabIndex:-1}),r.a.createElement("span",{className:"icon icon-close",onClick:u,onKeyDown:u,role:"button","aria-label":"Hide answer",tabIndex:-1})),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer",style:{maxHeight:l?"700px":0}},r.a.createElement("p",null,n)))});g.defaultProps={small:!1};var y=r.a.memo(g);n(62),t.default=function(){return r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement("a",{className:"anchor",id:"faq",href:"#faq"},"FAQ"),r.a.createElement("section",{className:"green faq"},r.a.createElement(h,{className:"faq-container"},r.a.createElement("h1",{className:"section-title"},"FAQ"),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"grid-container"},r.a.createElement(y,{question:"What is HackTJ?",answer:r.a.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ is a student-run hackathon where you will have 24 hours to learn how to code and/or work with your friends to make your idea come to life.")}),r.a.createElement(y,{question:"When is HackTJ?",answer:r.a.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ will start on Saturday, April 24 and run until Sunday, April 25.")}),r.a.createElement(y,{question:"Who can attend?",answer:r.a.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ is open to any and all current high school students. If you're not a high school student but would like to attend, consider coming as a judge, mentor, or volunteer.")}),r.a.createElement(y,{question:"Is there any cost?",answer:r.a.createElement("span",null,"Nope! Thanks to our sponsors, HackTJ is completely free!")}),r.a.createElement(y,{question:"Is there a deadline?",answer:r.a.createElement("span",null,"Registration for participants, judges, mentors, and volunteers opens on September 25 at 8 p.m. Registration for participants closes on October 16\u2014this is a hard deadline; we do not accept submissions after 8 p.m. Judges, mentors, and volunteers will be able to register until the start of the event.")}),r.a.createElement(y,{question:"Do you have a code of conduct?",small:!0,answer:r.a.createElement("span",null,"Yes, good question! We have adopted the"," ",r.a.createElement(m.b,{to:"conduct.pdf",target:"_blank",rel:"noopener noreferrer"},"MLH code of conduct"),", which all attendees will be required to adhere to.")}),r.a.createElement(y,{question:"Isn't hacking illegal?",answer:r.a.createElement("span",null,'In the context of a hackathon, "hacking" is to build a real application over the length of the event. It\'s important to not confuse this with illegal hacking, which is gaining unauthorized access to a computer.')}),r.a.createElement(y,{question:"Do I need a team?",answer:r.a.createElement("span",null,"If you already have a team of 2-4 people you want to work with, that's awesome! If not don't worry because we'll have an opportunity for people to join a team if they need one.")}),r.a.createElement(y,{question:"What if I don't know how to code?",small:!0,answer:r.a.createElement("span",null,"Come to HackTJ! Coding is fun, creative, and an important skill, and HackTJ is the perfect way to learn. We'll have workshops and mentors to help guide you.")}),r.a.createElement(y,{question:"What prizes can I win?",answer:r.a.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ hosts prizes for the best projects in the following categories: Overall Hack, Web App, Mobile App,Design, Social Impact Hack, and Beginner Hack (first-year coder teams). Major League Hacking and some of our partners also host their own Sponsored Prizes, which you can explore when the 7.5 Devpost goes live.")}),r.a.createElement(y,{question:"How do I register?",answer:r.a.createElement("span",null,'At 8 p.m. on September 25, a button will appear at the top of the site. Click this, and then you will be redirected to a page where you can click the appropriate form. If you\'re interested in participating as a hacker in HackTJ, click the first button, that says "Participants". Fill out the questions. Near the end, there will be a few questions where you can upload your forms. In order to speed up the registration process, print out these forms, fill them out, and scan them beforehand.')}),r.a.createElement(y,{question:"How are tickets decisions made?",small:!0,answer:r.a.createElement("span",null,"Tickets decisisons are made based on a variety of factors, including the registration time. Sign up quickly to increase the chance that you are given a HackTJ 7.5 ticket!")}),r.a.createElement("div",null)),r.a.createElement("p",{className:"large bottom-question"},"If your question is not answered here, just ask us:"," ",r.a.createElement("a",{href:"mailto:hello@hacktj.org",target:"_blank",rel:"noopener noreferrer"},"hello@hacktj.org"),"."))))}},27:function(e,t,n){var a;!function(){"use strict";var n={}.hasOwnProperty;function r(){for(var e=[],t=0;t<arguments.length;t++){var a=arguments[t];if(a){var o=typeof a;if("string"===o||"number"===o)e.push(a);else if(Array.isArray(a)&&a.length){var i=r.apply(null,a);i&&e.push(i)}else if("object"===o)for(var s in a)n.call(a,s)&&a[s]&&e.push(s)}}return e.join(" ")}e.exports?(r.default=r,e.exports=r):void 0===(a=function(){return r}.apply(t,[]))||(e.exports=a)}()},28:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.d(t,"f",(function(){return i})),n.d(t,"g",(function(){return s})),n.d(t,"h",(function(){return l})),n.d(t,"a",(function(){return u})),n.d(t,"j",(function(){return d})),n.d(t,"i",(function(){return f})),n.d(t,"d",(function(){return p})),n.d(t,"c",(function(){return h})),n.d(t,"b",(function(){return m})),n.d(t,"e",(function(){return v}));var a,r=n(5),o=n.n(r);function i(e,t){return void 0===e&&(e=""),void 0===t&&(t=a),t?e.split(" ").map((function(e){return t[e]||e})).join(" "):e}function s(e,t){var n={};return Object.keys(e).forEach((function(a){-1===t.indexOf(a)&&(n[a]=e[a])})),n}function l(e,t){for(var n,a=Array.isArray(t)?t:[t],r=a.length,o={};r>0;)o[n=a[r-=1]]=e[n];return o}var c="object"===typeof window&&window.Element||function(){};function u(e,t,n){if(!(e[t]instanceof c))return new Error("Invalid prop `"+t+"` supplied to `"+n+"`. Expected prop to be an instance of Element. Validation failed.")}var d=o.a.oneOfType([o.a.string,o.a.func,u,o.a.shape({current:o.a.any})]),f=o.a.oneOfType([o.a.func,o.a.string,o.a.shape({$$typeof:o.a.symbol,render:o.a.func}),o.a.arrayOf(o.a.oneOfType([o.a.func,o.a.string,o.a.shape({$$typeof:o.a.symbol,render:o.a.func})]))]),p={Fade:150,Collapse:350,Modal:300,Carousel:600},h=["in","mountOnEnter","unmountOnExit","appear","enter","exit","timeout","onEnter","onEntering","onEntered","onExit","onExiting","onExited"],m=["auto-start","auto","auto-end","top-start","top","top-end","right-start","right","right-end","bottom-end","bottom","bottom-start","left-end","left","left-start"],w=!("undefined"===typeof window||!window.document||!window.document.createElement);function g(e){return null==e?void 0===e?"[object Undefined]":"[object Null]":Object.prototype.toString.call(e)}function y(e){var t=typeof e;return null!=e&&("object"===t||"function"===t)}function b(e){if(function(e){return!(!e||"object"!==typeof e)&&"current"in e}(e))return e.current;if(function(e){if(!y(e))return!1;var t=g(e);return"[object Function]"===t||"[object AsyncFunction]"===t||"[object GeneratorFunction]"===t||"[object Proxy]"===t}(e))return e();if("string"===typeof e&&w){var t=document.querySelectorAll(e);if(t.length||(t=document.querySelectorAll("#"+e)),!t.length)throw new Error("The target '"+e+"' could not be identified in the dom, tip: check spelling");return t}return e}function E(e){return null!==e&&(Array.isArray(e)||w&&"number"===typeof e.length)}function v(e,t){var n=b(e);return t?E(n)?n:null===n?[]:[n]:E(n)?n[0]:n}},29:function(e,t,n){"use strict";function a(e,t){if(null==e)return{};var n,a,r={},o=Object.keys(e);for(a=0;a<o.length;a++)n=o[a],t.indexOf(n)>=0||(r[n]=e[n]);return r}n.d(t,"a",(function(){return a}))},61:function(e,t,n){},62:function(e,t,n){}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=8.3551943d.chunk.js.map